Md Naiemur Rahman

15/3 South Moisundi, Narinda, Dhaka. 01625639111 naiemjnu@gmail.com





SUMMARY

Creative and story-driven journalist with 4+ years of experience. Great storytelling skills and an excellent track record as a campus correspondent. As a law student having passion to gain and share knowledge in legal issues. Eager to contribute my best offering through my organizational and communication skills.



EDUCATION

LL.M | Jagannath University

01/2020 – Present CGPA-3.18 out of 4

LL.B Honours | Jagannath University

12/2015 - 12/2019 CGPA-3.03 out of 4

HSC (Science) | Shahid Syed Nazrul Islam College- Mymensingh.

05/2012 – 05/2014 GPA-4.80 out of 5

SSC (Science) | Tatihati Ideal School- Sherpur.

02/2010-05/2012 GPA-5 out of 5



SKILLS

- Drafting
- News and feature writing

- MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- Ability to work under pressure

EXPERIENCE

Research Executive | Saifur Rahman & Associates.

07/2020 - present

Jagannath University Correspondent | Daily Inqilab.

03/2017 - present

Executive Member | Jagannath University Journalists' Association.

08/2017 - 03/2019

Cultural Affairs Secretary | Consumer Youth of BD, CYB-JnU.

05/2018 - 10/2019



LANGUAGE

- Bangla and English
- Native or Bilingual

B

CONFERENCES

- Communication and Techniques: Training on Digital Rights/Safety, Media Laws and Media Ethics arranged by DW Akademie and Article 19. (Oct 2021)
- Basic Journalism Training and Workshop organized by Jagannath University Journalists' Association. (Jan 2016)
- Two-day long National Campus Journalism Fest hosted by Shahjalal University of Science and Technology (SUST) press club. (June 2018)
- Two-day long National Campus Journalism Fest Hosted by Chittagong University Journalists' Association. (Jul 2019)



REFERENCE

Md. Saifur Rahman Advocate, Supreme Court of Bangladesh

Cell: 01711337404

Email: sfradvocate@gmail.com